

# Feros Djahani Front-End Developer (Industrial Mechanic)

**Feros Djahani** Marie Juchacz Straße 42a

52349. Düren

0049/17645812584

Email:

f.djahani@outlook.de

Portfolio:

www.feros-djahani.developerakademie.net

# **About Me**

I am a German-speaking Front-End Developer with experience in building web apps with JavaScript & Angular. You can find my projects that including responsive websites and business apps in my public portfolio. I started my IT journey by coding small websites at home and watching other tutorials. During my current job as an industrial mechanic, I found that the part of work I enjoyed the most was always related to software. So I decided to amplify my IT knowledge and gain experience in web development. I am looking forward to building on my experience and starting my career in IT in a junior developer position.

#### Main Stack:

- JavaScript
- TypeScript, Angular
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

#### Side Stack:

- Git, APIs (REST), Google Firebase

# **Skills**

- Top Motivated: During the Days in the Week I had to work on a full-time job and after a day at work I went to my computer to code at night and also through the weekends. I have a history of doing a good job, so if it gets hard or if it is no fun, I do not complain.
- Building Applications with JavaScript & Angular: I built landing pages and several web apps, as well as OOP-based Jump-and-Run-Games with the respective technologies.
- Working in a Software Team: During learning coding, I did several group projects where I learned how to develop a software project in a team.
- High sense of responsibility: I am used to taking responsibility and working diligently, as I always did in my job as an industrial mechanic.

# **Professional Experience**

# Young Capital / Telephone Account Manager

JAN 2022 - PRESENT, Home-Office

- Handling individual customer calls
- Responsibility for regular KPI-Report to management

#### Ralf Winkler Fensterbau / Industrial Mechanic

JUL 2021 - OCT 2021, DUEREN

- Installation of manufactured front doors and windows according to customer requirements
- Production of custom-made windows
- Repair work on roller shutters and awnings on site at the customer

# **Industrial Mechanic** / Temp Agencies

(Go Work Solutions, Zeitfuchs, AMB Zeitarbeit, etc.)

NOV 2020 - JUL 2021

- Manufacturing of components according to customer requirements
- Maintenance work on the individual machines
- •

### **RWE Power AG / Industrial Mechanic**

AUG 2016 - AUG 2020, NIEDERAUßEM COLOGNE

- Repair machine components
- Weld individual assemblies together
- Safe handling of the operation of necessary machines in the production process

#### **Education**

# **Developer Akademie /** JavaScript & Angular Web Development Training

NOV 2021 - DEC 2022, Munich

Project based coding academy. Main Stack: JavaScript, Angular

Portfolio: www.feros-djahani.developerakademie.net

Extensive Coding School, Learning Front-End Development, Coding, Agile Project Management, and building several projects in teams and alone.

# RWE Power AG/IHK Cologne / Industrial Mechanic Training

AUG 2016 - AUG 2020, NIEDERAUßEM COLOGNE

- Theoretical and practical introduction to the operation of individual machines
- Theoretical and practical introduction to several work processes such as turning, milling, and welding
- Intensive preparation for the theoretical and practical final exam

## Languages

German: fluent English: fluent Farsi: native